[{"answer": " Hello, Alex.  Its so nice to meet you.  My name is Amber, and Im a mento", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 13, "question": "", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " Hi, Amber.  Its nice to meet you", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Hello, Alex.  Its so nice to meet you.  My name is Amber, and Im a mento", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " So, where do you come from", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 18, "question": " Hi, Amber.  Its nice to meet you", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " From Chicago", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 19, "question": " So, where do you come from", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " Well, youre pretty far away from home then", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 20, "question": " From Chicago", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " Yes, pretty far", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 21, "question": " Well, youre pretty far away from home then", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " I think youre going to like it at this college.  Youll get to meet a lot of ne", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 22, "question": " Yes, pretty far", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " Great", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 26, "question": " I think youre going to like it at this college.  Youll get to meet a lot of ne", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " How is the orientation going so far?  Have you found the sessions helpful", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 27, "question": " Great", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " I have.  They all seemed to give us useful information.  There is so much ne", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 31, "question": " How is the orientation going so far?  Have you found the sessions helpful", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " Dont worry about that.  Today is just an introduction.  As your mentor, Ill b", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 35, "question": " I have.  They all seemed to give us useful information.  There is so much ne", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " Thank you", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 39, "question": " Dont worry about that.  Today is just an introduction.  As your mentor, Ill b", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " Do you have any specific questions youd like to ask me today", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 40, "question": " Thank you", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " Yeah, I have one.  I was wondering about the grading system at the college.  I", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 41, "question": " Do you have any specific questions youd like to ask me today", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " Sure.  I can help explain that to you.  Basically, grades range from an A, whic", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 45, "question": " Yeah, I have one.  I was wondering about the grading system at the college.  I", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " I think so.  F is failing, and everything else is passing the class", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 50, "question": " Sure.  I can help explain that to you.  Basically, grades range from an A, whic", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " Yeah, thats right", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 51, "question": " I think so.  F is failing, and everything else is passing the class", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " So I could get all Ds and still graduate", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 52, "question": " Yeah, thats right", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " No, that you couldnt do.  You see, each grade you get in a class is converte", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 53, "question": " So I could get all Ds and still graduate", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " What about an F", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 58, "question": " No, that you couldnt do.  You see, each grade you get in a class is converte", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " You get no points for an F because thats a failing grade", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 59, "question": " What about an F", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " OK", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 60, "question": " You get no points for an F because thats a failing grade", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " You get points for every grade you receive from each class.  Now to graduate", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 61, "question": " OK", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " I think so", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 66, "question": " You get points for every grade you receive from each class.  Now to graduate", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " Here at the college, you have to have a minimum GPA or grade point averag", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 67, "question": " I think so", "qSentId": 66},{"answer": " I got it", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 71, "question": " Here at the college, you have to have a minimum GPA or grade point averag", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " Good, its important to understand because the grades you receive affect you", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 75, "question": " I got it", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " Im gonna try, but Ive never been a great student", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 79, "question": " Good, its important to understand because the grades you receive affect you", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " Well, we can help you with that too.  Our mentor program offers study session", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 80, "question": " Im gonna try, but Ive never been a great student", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " How do I use those services", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 84, "question": " Well, we can help you with that too.  Our mentor program offers study session", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " Once the semester starts, youll get an email from me with the dates and time", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 85, "question": " How do I use those services", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " I dont have to sign up and pay or anything", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 89, "question": " Once the semester starts, youll get an email from me with the dates and time", "qSentId": 88},{"answer": " Nope, its all free and you dont have to register either", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 90, "question": " I dont have to sign up and pay or anything", "qSentId": 89},{"answer": " That sounds great", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 91, "question": " Nope, its all free and you dont have to register either", "qSentId": 90},{"answer": " Well, were here to help you.  So, please email me or call me if you have an", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 92, "question": " That sounds great", "qSentId": 91},{"answer": " Thank you so much.  I will", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 97, "question": " Well, were here to help you.  So, please email me or call me if you have an", "qSentId": 96},{"answer": " Youre welcome.  Have a great rest of the day at the orientation", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 98, "question": " Thank you so much.  I will", "qSentId": 97},{"answer": " You too", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 99, "question": " Youre welcome.  Have a great rest of the day at the orientation", "qSentId": 98},{"answer": " Bye-bye", "docId": "06-05", "aSentId": 100, "question": " You too", "qSentId": 99}]
